http://www.exactseek.com/privacy.html

Privacy Policy Overview
This Privacy Policy applies where we, Jayde Online Inc., acts as a data controller or data processor with regard to all individuals including EU individuals under the General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR").
Registration
Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Services including name, address, telephone number. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (e.g. billing purposes). ExactSeek does not rent or sell email addresses nor any other personal data, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances.
However, in instances where ExactSeek and a partner jointly promote a Service, ExactSeek may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, email address, and URL of persons who subscribed to the Service in order to allow the partner to succesfully deliver the promoted Service. In such an instance, the partner may not not use personal information for any other purpose.
ExactSeek.com may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Members provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Members). As explained in more detail to the right, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear in our newsletters or on our network.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. ExactSeek.com may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. If you are a Member, we will use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information.
Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control the use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.
Security
Your personal information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to ExactSeek staff.
ExactSeek does not store any credit card information. Purchases made on ExactSeek are processed either by PayPal or Stripe.com.
Additional Rights
You have the right to request the data we have stored, as well as the right to have that data erased and to withdraw consent to further process your data.
Change of Ownership
In the event of a change in ownership, or a direct merger or acquisition of ExactSeek.com with another entity or multiple entities, all (or select aspects) of ExactSeek.com's customer information (including email addresses) may be transferred to a separate entity or entities. All ExactSeek.com subscribers and registered users will be notified of any change in ownership, merger or acquisition of ExactSeek.com's assets by a third party by email announcement or through prominently placed notices on the web site. Subscribers and users may choose to access and modify any of their registration and subscription information at that time.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
ExactSeek may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change.
Data Collection and Usage
There are two types of data we collect, information collected automatically "usage data" and information you provide to us "service data".
When you visit our websites we collect usage data such as (but not limited to) IP address, geo-location information, device type, operating system and Internet browser type, referral URL and standard web log data. This usage data may be processed for our legitimate interests namely monitoring, and improving our website and services.
When you voluntarily use tools or services on our website we may collect service data such as (but not limited to) Name, Email Address, IP Address and the date of your submission. This service data may be processed to provide our services, maintain a record of those services, and to communicate with you based on your consent.
ExactSeek offers four types of site listings - Standard, Featured, Paid Inclusion and Local Search. The information collected for each of these services, and how that information is used, is noted below:
Standard Listings: Email address and URL. Used in our newsletters (opt-in only). URL only provided to EntireWeb.com for inclusion in their search engine index.
Featured Listings: Email address, URL, Title, Description and Keyword term. Your email address is NOT shared.
Paid Inclusion Listings: Email address and URL. Your email address is not shared, but your site URL is provided to Entireweb.com for inclusion in their search engine index.
Traffic Listings: Email address, URL and Category. All information is public. Your billing email address is kept private.
ExactSeek Standard listings are free and the information collected is not shared with third parties, except as noted above. However, we may disclose personal information collected, if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that the law requires such disclosure or other special cases described below.
Membership is required under a valid, verified email address in order for you to submit your website to our free Standard Listing program. Upon the creation of a new member account, and in lieu of a site submission fee, you will be subscribed to one of our newsletter publications, ExactSeek News, or SiteProNews.
ExactSeek reserves the right to use the contact information collected during site submission to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to provide free newsletters (ExactSeek News, SiteProNews), to inform you of additions to the Jayde Online Network of web sites, or to send announcements and carefully screened offers and information on behalf of our partners or advertisers.
You may remove yourself from any or all of our newsletter, notice and announcement mailings at anytime using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes a valid email address and unsubscribe link which you can use to remove yourself from future mailings. If you encounter problems in this regard, contact abuse [at] exactseek.com. Our turnaround time for responding to unsubscribe requests is generally 1 business day.
Data Sharing
When you voluntarily use tools or services that involve publication of your information on our website this data may be available via the internet. We cannot prevent the use (or misuse) of such information by others.
When you voluntarily use tools or services that involve submission of your information to third parties, we act as an agent for you to provide your information to a third party for a specific purpose. Each third party will act as a data controller in that instance.
Data may be shared if it is required to comply with requests from courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies, and other public and government authorities.
Questions or Suggestions
Questions or suggestions may be sent to:
Your use of this website constitutes acceptance of the ExactSeek.com Privacy Policy
Jayde Online, Inc. © 2020, All Rights Reserved.
